
<resource xsi:schemaLocation="http://datacite.org/schema/kernel-4 https://schema.datacite.org/meta/kernel-4.4/metadata.xsd">
	<identifier relatedidentifierType="URL">https://www.kaggle.com/datasets/jessicali9530/animal-crossing-new-horizons-nookplaza-dataset/data</identifier>

<creator>
	<creatorName nameType="Personal">Li Jessica</creatorName>
</creator>
<title>Animal Crossing New Horizons Catalog</title>
<publisher>Kaggle: Data science company</publisher>
<publicationYear>2020</publicationYear>
<subject>Simulations</subject>
<descriptions>
	<description descriptionType="Other">A comprehensive inventory of ACNH items, villagers, clothing, fish/bugs etc</description>
	<description descriptionType="Other">This dataset comes from this spreadsheet, a comprehensive Item Catalog for Animal Crossing New Horizons (ACNH). As described by Wikipedia,ACNH is a life simulation game released by Nintendo for Nintendo Switch on March 20, 2020. It is the fifth main series title in the Animal Crossing series and, with 5 million digital copies sold, has broken the record for Switch title with most digital units sold in a single month. In New Horizons, the player assumes the role of a customizable character who moves to a deserted island. Taking place in real-time, the player can explore the island in a nonlinear fashion, gathering and crafting items, catching insects and fish, and developing the island into a community of anthropomorphic animals.</description>
	<description descriptionType="Other">There are 30 csvs each listing various items, villagers, clothing, and other collectibles from the game. The data was collected by a dedicated group of AC fans who continue to collaborate and build this spreadsheet for public use. The database contains the original data and full list of contributors and raw data. At the time of writing, the only difference between the spreadsheet and this version is that the Kaggle version omits all columns with images of the items, but is otherwise identical.</description>
	description descriptionType="Other">Thanks to every contributor listed on the spreadsheet! Please attribute this spreadsheet and group for any use of the data. They also have a Discord server linked in the spreadsheet in case you want to contact them.</description>
</descriptions>
</resource>
